BLESSING AMAZUIRO CHINAEMEREM

Address: Surulere, Lagos

Email: amazuiro@yahoo.com Phone number: 08160999831

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a creative person with very good organizational and management skills. I have good communication skills, clear and logical mind with a practical approach to problem solving and I drive to see things to completion working both within a team and unsupervised. I have over two years of experience in sales management and marketing strategies implementation with an impressive track record. I have a high productivity record with data analytics and troubleshooting skills that will be very useful to your company.

EDUCATION

University of Nigeria, Nsukka, Enugu State 2013 – 2017 B.Sc. Microbiology

(Second class upper division)

WORK EXPERIENCE

DigifyNG (October 2020 - December 2020)

Intern

- Learned digital marketing skills such as content creation, community management, search engine optimization, social media analytics and Facebook ads manager.
- Worked with a team of 10 people to generate digital marketing strategies for a business.
- Successfully created live briefs for 7 businesses and ensured the deliverables were up to standard.

Pearls Africa (January 2021 - March 2021)

Frontend Intern

- Developed functional websites using HTML, CSS and Javascipt.
- Work with Senior developer to write codes from scratch.
- Edited existing codes to improve the user experience.

CERTIFICATIONS AND TRAININGS

Facebook Blueprint November 2020

Digital Marketing Associate

Jobberman June 2020

Soft Skills Training

Google 2020 June 2020

Fundamentals of Digital marketing

Codecademy May 2020

Data science career path

Excel for business

Python for data science

Novelle Center April 2019

Basic first aid Environmental Impact Assessment

Health and safety

SKILLS

- Excellent analytical, negotiating, influencing, interpersonal and communication skills both written & verbally as well as work effectively under pressure & to meet deadlines
- Good knowledge in designing new and engaging content develop communication & customer engagement strategies, including contests and giveaways, to enhance brandawareness.
- Good knowledge of data analytics tools for business and arranging data properly for visualization.
- Active listener both within a team and to superiors.
- Good team player.
- Proficient use of Microsoft Office Suite.
- Critical thinking and problem solving skills
- High digital literacy.
- Emotional intelligence and soft skills.